(Sheldon:)That's Leonard's.
(Amy:)Children's toy.
(Sheldon:)One Game of Thrones
collector's edition Longclaw sword.
(Sheldon:)Leonard and I bought that together.
(Sheldon:)That's a bit of an ethical conundrum.
(Sheldon:)I'll keep it.
So, what's your plan moving forward?
I suppose I'll have to find and cultivate
a new roommate.
(Sheldon:)What a task that will be.
(Sheldon:)Do you know how uncivilized
Leonard was when I took him in?
(Sheldon:)- No.
- It took me forever...
(Sheldon:)...to get him on a bathroom schedule.
(Sheldon:)He would just go
whenever the mood struck him.
- Like a dog boy.
- Exactly.
(Amy:)What if you could find a roommate
who was a scientist...
(Amy:)...and already familiar and comfortable
with your ways?
(Sheldon:)That would be ideal.
(Sheldon:)If a person like that existed,
I would sign on, no further questions asked.
(Amy:)Great, here I am.